Alexis Cousins

Junior Front End Developer

Contact

Address

North Shore, AUK, 0620

Phone

+6421 215 0163

E-mail

cousins.dev@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexis-cousins-06b7412

Skills

Agile Workflow

Very Good

Software Best Practices

Very Good

Written Communication

Excellent

Customer service

Excellent

Web development projects

Excellent

Programming Languages

Good

Responsive design

Forthcoming diploma recipient with one years experience in web design and development, with a creative fire and passion for high quality outcomes. I am an ambitious, career-focused job seeker, excited to obtain an entry-level front-end developer position to help launch my career and gain invaluable industry experience while achieving company goals.

Work History

2020-02 -2021-01

Service Coordinator

Aotea Electric Auckland, North Shore, Auckland

- Maintained effective customer service by responding to service requests quickly to increase overall weekly jobs by 20%.
- Quickly learnt and navigated a complex business management system to manage 15 employees, including some payroll and client account responsibilities.
- Maintained critical company and client data on a week by week basis.
- Employed personal systems to optimize team processes and increase overall efficiency.

2015-01 -2020-01

Trade Team Member

Bunnings Warehouse, North Shore, Auckland

- Contributed to team success by completing jobs quickly and accurately.
- Trained new team members by relaying information on company procedures and safety requirements.
- Maintained productive, efficient approach to all tasks.
- Managed Trade Customer accounts with keen eye to detail.

Education

2021-01 -2021-12

Diploma: Web And UX Design

Yoobee College - Auckland, New Zealand

 Currently completing my Level 6 Diploma in Web and UX Design.



Spanish

Good

- Designed, developed and deployed an original portfolio site using Nuxt and Tailwind.
- Produced a full-stack C2C platform to combat the issue of fast fashion in New Zealand.
- One year of experience employing UX design process.
- Worked as both developer and designer for a range of projects, from and NZ-based journey planning web-app to a blog site for students.

2016-02 -2019-11

Bachelor of Communications: Communications

Auckland University of Technology - Auckland, New Zealand